JAMES LEWIS

6/126 Mitchell Street, Brunswick East · 0422732175

Jamesglew@gmail.com · <u>LinkedIn Profile</u> · <u>Github</u>

Junior software developer with a passion for user centered design principles. I aim to provide the best possible experience for users and the client.

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

UI/UX AND FRONT END DEVELOPER, UNEEK

CONTRACTOR

Frontend and UI/UX development using React, Typescript and Material UI.

February 2020 - November 2020

UI/UX AND FRONT END DEVELOPER, DIGITIZATION OF ABORIGINAL HISTORY PROJECT

UI/UX DESIGNER

User experience designer for final year project. This role involved wireframe design, usability testing and prototype creation.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Front end development using android studio and kotlin. This role involved UI creation, testing, bug fixing and requirement gathering.

JANUARY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2016

FIBRE OPTIC NETWORK DESIGNER, BIARRI NETWORKS

PRODUCT TESTING

Product tester for Biarri's automated network design tool. This role involved software release testing, client liaisons and requirements testing.

PROJECT PLANNING & TEAM LEADERSHIP

Team leader for design corrections. This role involved teaching others, scheduling in company and with clients.

CLIENT LIAISON

Consultant for quality assurance meetings and construction design meetings when working with Google Fibre.

EDUCATION

FEBRUARY 2021

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, SWINBURNE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY Majoring in Software Development and co-majoring in Cyber Security

November 2014

BACHELOR OF **S**CIENCE, **S**WINBURNE UNIVERSITY OF **T**ECHNOLOGY **Majoring in Biochemistry and co-majoring in Advanced Chemistry**

SKILLS

- Kotlin
- C++/C#
- Python
- CSS/HTML
- UI/UX Design
- Material UI
- Git
- Agile Development
- SQL Databases
- Android Development
- React
- Redux

- Project Management
- Team Leadership Experience
- Technical Writing & Presentation
- Client Relations
- GIS Data Systems
- Cisco Certified Network Associate
- 120 WPM Typing Speed

REFERENCES

References will be provided if requested.